[{"answer": "He was somebody who didn't know any boundaries, really, that didn't quite clearly see the lines, the lines that all of us need to see in the light, a line between right and wrong.", "docId": "111112pmt", "aSentId": 5, "question": "What was that man really like?", "qSentId": 4}, {"answer": "I think because he -- he tried.", "docId": "111112pmt", "aSentId": 19, "question": "Why did you feel differently about your father?", "qSentId": 18}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "111112pmt", "aSentId": 30, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 29}, {"answer": "Yes, I did.", "docId": "111112pmt", "aSentId": 33, "question": "Did you feel that when you finished it, that you -- when you closed the book and thought, That's my life?", "qSentId": 32}, {"answer": "Because I just thought of you as this funny guy who does Donald Trump and Bill Clinton on \"Saturday Night Live.\"", "docId": "111112pmt", "aSentId": 45, "question": "Why?", "qSentId": 44}, {"answer": "Well, it's -- that's a lot -- that's a lot of -- that's a lot to think about.", "docId": "111112pmt", "aSentId": 49, "question": "What -- what's that done to your life?", "qSentId": 48}, {"answer": "ORGAN: And it went on.", "docId": "111112pmt", "aSentId": 52, "question": "I spent most of my life, I guess, recovering from moments like that, you know?", "qSentId": 51}, {"answer": "Do you have any theories yourself about why your mother...", "docId": "111112pmt", "aSentId": 69, "question": "It does happen, you know?", "qSentId": 68}, {"answer": "I think she was abused.", "docId": "111112pmt", "aSentId": 72, "question": "She'd been abused?", "qSentId": 71}, {"answer": "Well, I -- I called her and said, I'm -- I'm in therapy for trauma and child abuse and -- and worse.", "docId": "111112pmt", "aSentId": 78, "question": "As you got older, what was your relationship with your mother like?", "qSentId": 77}, {"answer": "Not until her deathbed.", "docId": "111112pmt", "aSentId": 87, "question": "Did you have any more contact with her?", "qSentId": 86}, {"answer": "I felt nothing.", "docId": "111112pmt", "aSentId": 89, "question": "And how did that make you feel, when she died?", "qSentId": 88}, {"answer": "Well, it's not surprising to me that you're so emotional about this.", "docId": "111112pmt", "aSentId": 91, "question": "I was very moved by my father, you know?", "qSentId": 90}, {"answer": "I think because he -- he tried.", "docId": "111112pmt", "aSentId": 97, "question": "Why did you feel differently about your father?", "qSentId": 96}, {"answer": "Yes, sure.", "docId": "111112pmt", "aSentId": 102, "question": "Can I have a tissue or something?", "qSentId": 101}, {"answer": "I don't think so.", "docId": "111112pmt", "aSentId": 108, "question": "Was he aware of what your mother was doing?", "qSentId": 107}, {"answer": "He was apologetic for his own negligence towards you.", "docId": "111112pmt", "aSentId": 110, "question": "He -- he was never there, you know?", "qSentId": 109}, {"answer": "I guess Clinton is the one that -- that you get the most mileage out of.", "docId": "111112pmt", "aSentId": 153, "question": "Which was your favorite?", "qSentId": 152}, {"answer": "Oh...", "docId": "111112pmt", "aSentId": 158, "question": "Where?", "qSentId": 157}, {"answer": "No, just right before it.", "docId": "111112pmt", "aSentId": 168, "question": "... colonoscopy?", "qSentId": 167}, {"answer": "Once in a while.", "docId": "111112pmt", "aSentId": 179, "question": "So you do do it, you say?", "qSentId": 178}, {"answer": "My favorite was Donald Trump.", "docId": "111112pmt", "aSentId": 190, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 189}, {"answer": "Well, he's been amazing.", "docId": "111112pmt", "aSentId": 215, "question": "What do you make of his impression?", "qSentId": 214}, {"answer": "I guess from my mom.", "docId": "111112pmt", "aSentId": 229, "question": "Where go you get the ability to do impressions from, do you think?", "qSentId": 228}, {"answer": "Really good.", "docId": "111112pmt", "aSentId": 232, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 231}, {"answer": "Coaches, teachers, people in the neighborhood.", "docId": "111112pmt", "aSentId": 240, "question": "Who would she do?", "qSentId": 239}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "111112pmt", "aSentId": 244, "question": "And would make you laugh?", "qSentId": 243}, {"answer": "It just would change her.", "docId": "111112pmt", "aSentId": 249, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 248}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "111112pmt", "aSentId": 266, "question": "Have you been able to forgive her, in your mind?", "qSentId": 265}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "111112pmt", "aSentId": 284, "question": "Well, I was going to ask you, were you ever high when you were on the air?", "qSentId": 283}, {"answer": "No!", "docId": "111112pmt", "aSentId": 290, "question": "Never tempted?", "qSentId": 289}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "111112pmt", "aSentId": 300, "question": "Are you clean now?", "qSentId": 299}, {"answer": "Well, I haven't done as well as I wanted to with that, but it's been going pretty well.", "docId": "111112pmt", "aSentId": 302, "question": "You don't drink or take drugs at all?", "qSentId": 301}, {"answer": "I think so.", "docId": "111112pmt", "aSentId": 316, "question": "Are you happier than you've been before?", "qSentId": 315}, {"answer": "I don't know.", "docId": "111112pmt", "aSentId": 323, "question": "Do you think \"Saturday Night Live\" co-stars will be shocked by this book?", "qSentId": 322}, {"answer": "I don't know.", "docId": "111112pmt", "aSentId": 327, "question": "Did they know about your mother and stuff?", "qSentId": 326}, {"answer": "It was pretty damned bad.", "docId": "111112pmt", "aSentId": 334, "question": "How bad was the incident?", "qSentId": 333}, {"answer": "Actually, from -- I think that in the book it says the offices.", "docId": "111112pmt", "aSentId": 338, "question": "From the studio?", "qSentId": 337}, {"answer": "It did.", "docId": "111112pmt", "aSentId": 351, "question": "How could this have been going on with this guy, who just seems like he's the happiest, funniest guy you'd ever meet?", "qSentId": 350}, {"answer": "Well, I'm doing \"Are We There Yet?\"", "docId": "111112pmt", "aSentId": 356, "question": "What are you doing career-wise now?", "qSentId": 355}, {"answer": "I just want to play Truman Capote on Broadway.", "docId": "111112pmt", "aSentId": 363, "question": "What ambitions do you have professionally and personally?", "qSentId": 362}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "111112pmt", "aSentId": 409, "question": "Do you?", "qSentId": 408}, {"answer": "He was somebody who didn't know of any boundaries really, that didn't quite clearly see the lines, the lines that all of us need to see in life, the line between right and wrong.", "docId": "111112pmt", "aSentId": 418, "question": "What was that man really like?", "qSentId": 417}, {"answer": "BRAMOFF: Well, I think that with me, a couple things went wrong.", "docId": "111112pmt", "aSentId": 423, "question": "What went wrong?", "qSentId": 422}, {"answer": "I'm not going to defend my e-mails.", "docId": "111112pmt", "aSentId": 441, "question": "I mean, that to me was -- it isn't worse than the corruption, but it certainly left a pretty bad taste when you read that, you know?", "qSentId": 440}, {"answer": "Well, a number of things.", "docId": "111112pmt", "aSentId": 452, "question": "What do you think was the worst thing you did?", "qSentId": 451}, {"answer": "I didn't consciously feel I was doing that.", "docId": "111112pmt", "aSentId": 465, "question": "Did you know as you were doing it you were breaking the law?", "qSentId": 464}, {"answer": "Well, there are a lot of lines and a lot of these lines --", "docId": "111112pmt", "aSentId": 476, "question": "H many other people at the time were crossing the line do you really think?", "qSentId": 475}, {"answer": "A healthy percentage.", "docId": "111112pmt", "aSentId": 480, "question": "What would you guess from your knowledge of the system?", "qSentId": 479}, {"answer": "Twenty.", "docId": "111112pmt", "aSentId": 482, "question": "What kind of percentage?", "qSentId": 481}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "111112pmt", "aSentId": 484, "question": "Twenty percent of every lobbyist was doing the same kind of thing?", "qSentId": 483}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "111112pmt", "aSentId": 487, "question": "BRAMOFF: Have been held to account?", "qSentId": 486}, {"answer": "He's the leader of the free world.", "docId": "111112pmt", "aSentId": 532, "question": "What was your reaction to that?", "qSentId": 531}, {"answer": "It's completely implausible he wouldn't have been aware with you.", "docId": "111112pmt", "aSentId": 536, "question": "Come out and say he's my best friend and, you know, I was hand in glove with him?", "qSentId": 535}, {"answer": "Well, I -- yes, I can't speak for him but he's a politician.", "docId": "111112pmt", "aSentId": 540, "question": "How could he not know who you were?", "qSentId": 539}, {"answer": "I guess what happened was there was an article in \"The Washington Post\" and then immediately after the article, the Congress called for hearings and the Justice Department to get involved.", "docId": "111112pmt", "aSentId": 547, "question": "Where were you, how did you know?", "qSentId": 546}, {"answer": "Yes, but the general level of corruption that was going on, this is very bad for American politics.", "docId": "111112pmt", "aSentId": 564, "question": "You mean in terms of campaign contributions and things like that?", "qSentId": 563}, {"answer": "I want people to feel is I want them to know what this system is.", "docId": "111112pmt", "aSentId": 572, "question": "What do you want people to feel?", "qSentId": 571}, {"answer": "Well, whether it's criminal or not, or it should be criminal maybe is the question.", "docId": "111112pmt", "aSentId": 586, "question": "What kind of thing do you think is going on that is criminal in your mind?", "qSentId": 585}, {"answer": "Well, I just finished writing a book.", "docId": "111112pmt", "aSentId": 593, "question": "What are you doing with your life at the moment?", "qSentId": 592}, {"answer": "I don't -- I have a job doing that.", "docId": "111112pmt", "aSentId": 596, "question": "Do you have a job at the moment?", "qSentId": 595}, {"answer": "That's it, right now.", "docId": "111112pmt", "aSentId": 598, "question": "That's it?", "qSentId": 597}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "111112pmt", "aSentId": 603, "question": "All gone?", "qSentId": 602}, {"answer": "I haven't added it all up, but it was tens of millions.", "docId": "111112pmt", "aSentId": 606, "question": "You're aware of that?", "qSentId": 605}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "111112pmt", "aSentId": 608, "question": "All gone?", "qSentId": 607}, {"answer": "I mean, money is a tool.", "docId": "111112pmt", "aSentId": 611, "question": "What do you feel about it now that you don't have any?", "qSentId": 610}, {"answer": "Because I felt I got this money to do good things with it.", "docId": "111112pmt", "aSentId": 618, "question": "Why did you give it away?", "qSentId": 617}, {"answer": "Well, I have a I have a sense of humor, so most of the time I laughed, if they were good jokes.", "docId": "111112pmt", "aSentId": 648, "question": "How did you feel being the butt of the jokes?", "qSentId": 647}, {"answer": "Well, I didn't have to explain it to my children.", "docId": "111112pmt", "aSentId": 658, "question": "How have you explained it to your children?", "qSentId": 657}, {"answer": "Well, I don't know that there's a single thing I regret most.", "docId": "111112pmt", "aSentId": 667, "question": "What was the single thing you regret most?", "qSentId": 666}, {"answer": "I'm in my 35th.", "docId": "111112pmt", "aSentId": 678, "question": "In all the time that you've been in Congress, how many years now?", "qSentId": 677}, {"answer": "No, it's not.", "docId": "111112pmt", "aSentId": 689, "question": "Is that a good thing?", "qSentId": 688}, {"answer": "Well, I think we'll continue, but it will be done in a much more sophisticated and differently organized manner.", "docId": "111112pmt", "aSentId": 704, "question": "And whatever the merits of each of the individual interventions, there comes a point, doesn't there, when if America wants to compete with the likes of China, India and so on, then this constant marching around the world helping everyone has to take a bit of a back seat to helping America?", "qSentId": 703}, {"answer": "I suspect the problems that are embedded in terrorism -- in other words, cell groups, smaller groups of people who may, in fact, try to transport either a nuclear chemical or biological weapons in some form to the United States and create havoc in one or more of our major cities or through plagues or other diseases.", "docId": "111112pmt", "aSentId": 711, "question": "Who do you think is the biggest threat currently to America?", "qSentId": 710}, {"answer": "Well, I think Governor Romney has been the front-runner throughout this situation.", "docId": "111112pmt", "aSentId": 715, "question": "Who do you think is emerging, perhaps nobody is yet, as a genuine front-runner candidate?", "qSentId": 714}, {"answer": "I would say yes to both.", "docId": "111112pmt", "aSentId": 719, "question": "And can -- if he is, can he beat Barack Obama?", "qSentId": 718}]